Guide to the McCann-Erickson Audiovisual Collection, 1980s-1990s and undated RL.00863
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Original Videotapes, 1980s-1990s, 49 boxes
  - 543. Reel #1: New Products (Microwave). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Benihana: Judgment Day (Box 36)
    - Pillsbury Microwave Pizza: Right now (Box 36)
  - 544. Nestlé: Crunch Chocolate, Party Chocolate; Carrier Air Conditioner. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:20
    - Nestlé Crunch Chocolate (China) (Box 36)
    - Nestlé Party Chocolate (China) (Box 36)
    - Carrier Air Conditioner (Hong Kong) (Box 36)
  - 545. Nestlé (Brazil): Molico, Alternative Line. 1987. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Nestlé Molico Milk: Mum's Cuddling Dad (Box 36)
  - 546. Set One Hans Van Der Ros Presentation: Nestlé Growth Opportunities, Latin America. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 36)
    [See also Tape 550]
  - 547. (Nestlé) Effective Advertising by Ernst Schmid/Market Research Manager, Nestlé. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [A presentation looking at the effective spending of advertising money. A five-point plan to minimize large financial risks while making sure that money spent is used effectively: situation analysis; what to say to whom; how to say it; evaluation of final advertisement; campaign effectiveness. Plan is applied to the Nestlé brand; Barry Day helps with the application.]
    - Nescafé: Take a Pinch of… (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: Great Theory (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: Special Moments (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: The Presenter/Gareth Hunt (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: Gareth Hunt/3 Bean Trick (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: Gareth Hunt/3 Bean Trick (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: Gareth Hunt/3 Bean Trick (Box 36)
  - 548. Nestlé Corporate Presentation. 1985. Umatic. PAL. TRT: 30:00 (Box 36)
  - 549. Compilation Tape--Recent Nestlé Commercials. 1984. Umatic. PAL. TRT: 37:00
    - Nescafé: Saturday Morning (Australia) (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: Coming Home (Australia) (Box 36)
    - Tradiçao: Setimo Sentido (Brazil) (Box 36)
    - Tradiçao: Silent Movie (Brazil) (Box 36)
    - Casa Grande: Farm (Brazil) (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: Peter and Diane (England) (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: Trio (England) (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: Architect (Hong Kong) (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: Fashion Designer (Hong Kong) (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: Train (Italy) (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: Hausa (Nigeria) (Box 36)
    - Nescafé (Panama) (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: Airplane (Peru) (Box 36)
    - Nescafé (Thailand) (Box 36)
    - Decaf: Dancer (USA) (Box 36)
    - Granor (Venezuela) (Box 36)
    - President: Lord and Lady Cawdor (Japan) (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: Monaco--Iced (Japan) (Box 36)
    - Nescafé: NY (Japan) (Box 36)
    - Maggi: Onion Stock Cubes (Australia) (Box 36)
    - Maggi: Tomato Soup (Australia) (Box 36)
    - Maggi: Ripper Roast (Australia) (Box 36)
    - Maggi Cubes (Austria) (Box 36)
    - Maggi Mayonnaise (Ecuador) (Box 36)
    - Cook-in-the-Pot chicken product (England) (Box 36)
    - Dish of the Day (England) (Box 36)
    - 5 Minute Terrine: Young Man (Germany) (Box 36)
    - Gulasch Fix (Germany) (Box 36)
    - Maggi Seasoning (Hong Kong) (Box 36)
    - Maggi (Portugal) (Box 36)
    - Maggi (Portugal) (Box 36)
    - Maggi Cubes (Spain) (Box 36)
    - Maggi: Bases Cocinar (Spain) (Box 36)
    - Leite Moça (Brazil) (Box 36)
    - Leite Moça (Brazil) (Box 36)
    - Molico: Engineer (Brazil) (Box 36)
    - Molico: Cycling (Brazil) (Box 36)
    - Crema de Leite: Fruit Salad (Brazil) (Box 36)
    - Crema de Leite: Spaghetti (Brazil) (Box 36)
    - Leche Condensada (Chile) (Box 36)
    - Leche Condensada (Chile) (Box 36)
    - Crema Nestlé: Mixed Fruit (Chile) (Box 36)
    - Crema Nestlé: Chicken Dish (Chile) (Box 36)
    - Nido (Mexico) (Box 36)
    - Nido (Mexico) (Box 36)
    - Condensada: Strawberries (Peru) (Box 36)
    - Condensada: Mixed Fruit (Peru) (Box 36)
    - Condensada: Chocolate (Peru) (Box 36)
    - Nespray: Circus Chorus (Hong Kong) (Box 36)
    - UHT Milk: Wonderland (Hong Kong) (Box 36)
    - Nido (Japan) (Box 36)
    - UHT Milk (Thailand) (Box 36)
    - Quik: Wendy House/Bugs Bunny (Chile) (Box 36)
    - Quik: Bugs Bunny/Free Teeth (Chile) (Box 36)
    - Quik: Bugs Bunny/Quiky Toys (Chile) (Box 36)
    - Quik: Cartoon Characters (Chile) (Box 36)
    - Nesquick: Indians (Italy) (Box 36)
    - Nesquick: Frisby (Italy) (Box 36)
    - Nesquick: Penguin (Germany) (Box 36)
    - Nesquick: Planes (Germany) (Box 36)
    - Nesquick: Farm Scene (Spain) (Box 36)
    - Nesquick: Seaside (Spain) (Box 36)
    - Quik: Ping Pong (USA) (Box 36)
    - Quik: Ping Pong (USA) (Box 36)
    - Nesquick: Supershakers (U.K.) (Box 36)
  - 550. Hans Van Der Ros Presentation: Nestlé Grown Opportunities, Latin America. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 36)
    [See also Tape 546]
  - 551. Pillsbury Pizza Microwave. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Pillsbury Microwave: Snack/Right Now (Box 36)
  - 552. Recipe for Success--Cooking With Maggi (Germany, Spain, Mexico, Finland, UK). 1979. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 37)
    - Maggi: Potato Pizza (Germany) (Box 37)
    - Maggi: Kish (Germany) (Box 37)
    - Maggi: Sprouts/Soup (Germany) (Box 37)
    - Maggi: Cream of Mushroom Soup (Australia) (Box 37)
    - Maggi: Chicken Nootle Soup (Australia) (Box 37)
    - Maggi: Chicken Salsa (Mexico) (Box 37)
    - Maggi: Food Preparation (Spain) (Box 37)
    - Maggi: Condensed Recipe (Finland) (Box 37)
    - Crosse & Blackwell: Sweet & Sour Sauce (U.K.) (Box 37)
    - Crosse & Blackwell: Cook in the Pot (U.K.) (Box 37)
    - Crosse & Blackwell: Rice & Things (U.K.) (Box 37)
  - 553. Stork Margarine: Mrs. Bayles Trifle, Neighbours. 1986. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - Stork Margarine: Mrs. Bayles/Trifle (Box 37)
    - Stork Margarine: Neighbors (Box 37)
  - 554. Stork Compilation. 1988. Umatic. PAL. TRT: 3:00
    - Stork Margarine: Easy Cakes (Box 37)
    - Stork Margarine: Sandwiches (Box 37)
    - Stork Margarine: Sunday Lunch (Box 37)
    - Stork Margarine: Stir Fry (Box 37)
    - Stork Margarine: Kid's Stuff (Box 37)
    - Stork Margarine: Wedding Cake (Box 37)
    - Stork Margarine: Turkey Fetish (Box 37)
  - 555. Stork Fruit Cake Revised. 1988. Umatic. PAL. TRT: 00:30
    - Stork Margarine: Fruit Cake (reviesd) (Box 37)
  - 556. 1985 Supermarket T.V.C.'s. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Spartan Stores: Shop Rite Brand (Box 37)
    - D'AG: The Butcher (Box 37)
    - Goff--The Food Store: More Than Just Groceries (Box 37)
    - Shaw's: Homemade Food (Box 37)
    - Super Valu: Notes (Box 37)
    - Gateway Foods (Rainbow): Warehousse/Rain (Box 37)
    - Vons: Olympics (Box 37)
    - Associated Grocers (Mega Foods): Cheap Quality (Box 37)
    - Cub Foods: Can Opener (Box 37)
    - Stop & Shop: When Is It Time (Box 37)
    - Eagle: Oriental Cooking (Box 37)
  - 557. The USA Candy Industry. 1985. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - Brach's Peanut Cluster: Made With Care (Box 37)
    - Brach's Hard Candy: 200 Kinds (Box 37)
    - Cadbury's Chocolate Bars: Cow (Box 37)
    - Cadbury's Crème Eggs: Rabbit/Chicken (Box 37)
    - Peter Paul Mounds and Almond Joy: Tropical Paradise (Box 37)
    - York Peppermint Patty: Kids (Box 37)
    - Fanny Farmer Candy: 70 Varieties (Box 37)
    - Tic Tac Mints: Pendulum (Box 37)
    - Mon Cheri: Treat Yourself (Box 37)
    - Godiva Chocolates: Gold Box (Box 37)
    - Hershey's Chocolate Bar: Bluegrass Band (Box 37)
    - Kit Kat: Late Snack/Roar (Box 37)
    - Hershey's Take Five: Fast-Paced (Box 37)
    - Reese's Peanut Butter Cups: Horror Movie (Box 37)
    - Reese's Pieces Peanuts: Farmers (Box 37)
    - New Trail Granola Bar: Lip Synch (Box 37)
    - Good & Plenty: Train (Box 37)
    - Snickers: Business Woman (Box 37)
    - Milky Way: Roller Skates (Box 37)
    - Twix: More Than… (Box 37)
    - M& M's Chocolate Candies: Family Reunion (Box 37)
    - 3 Musketeers: Floating (Box 37)
    - Lifesavers Candy: Less Than 10 Calories (Box 37)
    - Baby Ruth/Butterfinger: Dick Clark (Box 37)
    - Nestlé Crunch: Traffic Cop (Box 37)
    - Nestlé Chocolate Bar: Passion (Box 37)
    - Velamints: Sledding (Box 37)
    - Tootsie Rolls: Becomes a Tootsie (Box 37)
    - Certs: Encounter Letter (Box 37)
    - Whitman's: Valentine's Day (Box 37)
  - 558. The USA Fast Foods Industry. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - McDonald's: Stranger in the House (Box 37)
    - McDonald's: U.S. Wins, You Win (Box 37)
    - Burger King: Emmanuel Lewis (Box 37)
    - Wendy's: Where's the Beef? (Box 37)
    - Wendy's: Where's the Beef?/$20,000 (Box 37)
    - Hardee's: Variety Selection (Box 37)
    - Hardee's: Something or Nothing (Box 37)
    - Pizza Hut: Car Choices (Box 37)
    - Pizza Hut: Texas Stadium (Box 37)
    - Domino's: Sportscasters (Box 37)
    - Godfather's: Gangster (Box 37)
    - Kentucky Fried Chicken: Exciting Memories (Box 37)
    - Kentucky Fried Chicken: Trivia Time Promo (Box 37)
    - Church's: More for Less (Box 37)
    - Long John Silver's: Start Fresh (Box 37)
    - Captain D's: Testimonials (Box 37)
  - 559. Van Den Bergh United States Tape. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Stork Packet: Chequer Cake (Box 37)
    - Stork SB: Taste Test Seven (Box 37)
    - Stork SB: Candid Camera/Janice Wallington (Box 37)
    - Stork SB: Laura Trott Smith (Box 37)
    - Stork SB: Piano Tuner (Box 37)
    - Stork SB: Mum for a Day (Box 37)
    - Stork SB: Mrs. Bayles Trifle (Box 37)
    - Blue Band: Doris Day (Box 37)
    - Blue Band: Feeling Good (Box 37)
    - Blue Band: Skipping (corn oil relaunch) (Box 37)
    - Flora: Watch (Box 37)
    - Flora: Supermarket (Box 37)
    - Flora: Architect (Box 37)
    - Flora: Just Like Dad (Box 37)
    - Flora: Mum (Box 37)
    - Flora: Little Things (Box 37)
    - Vitalite: Treat Your Body Right (Box 37)
    - Vitalite: As Wholesome As Your… (Box 37)
    - Outline: Wolf Whistle (Box 37)
    - Outline: Zip relaunch (Box 37)
    - Outline: Treats (Box 37)
    - Outline: Current Ad (Box 37)
    - St. Ivel Gold: Launch Aah! (Box 37)
    - St. Ivel Gold: Goldrush 2 (Box 37)
    - St. Ivel Gold: Farmer Lodge (Box 37)
    - St. Ivel Gold: Diving Board (Box 37)
    - St. Ivel Gold: Golf (Box 37)
    - Delight: Fat to Thin (Box 37)
    - Delight: Gloom to Cheer (Box 37)
    - Delight: Line extension (Box 37)
    - Delight: Taste of Good Health (Box 37)
    - Delight: Food montage (Box 37)
    - Delight: Billboard animatic (Box 37)
    - Krona: Parliament (Box 37)
    - Krona: Jogging (Box 37)
    - Krona: Stasbourg (Box 37)
    - Krona: Apple (Box 37)
    - Clover: Gruddocks (Box 37)
    - Clover: Foggy (Box 37)
    - Clover: Judi Dench (Box 37)
    - Meadowcup: More Moo (Box 37)
    - Golden Churn: On the Phone (Box 37)
    - BIC: Breakfast (Box 37)
    - Anchor: Rowboat/Children (Box 37)
    - Country Life: Quality Control (Box 37)
    - Lurpak: Butter Sailor (Box 37)
    - Cookeen: Lift Sausage Roll (Box 37)
    - White Cap: La Di Da (Box 37)
    - White Flora: Activities (Box 37)
    - Crisp n' Dry: Paper Towel/Chips (Box 37)
    - Crisp n' Dry: Flying Doughnuts (Box 37)
    - Mazola: Ear of Corn (Box 37)
    - Elmlea: Harry (Box 37)
  - 560. Spots: Wendy's/Where's the Beef. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Wendy's: Where's the Beef?/Ladies (Box 37)
    - Wendy's: Where's the Beef?/Men (Box 37)
  - 561. Wendy's Where's the Beef?. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 00:30
    - Wendy's: Where's the Beef?/Ladies (Box 37)
  - 562. Computer Material (for selection only). 1983. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 37)
  - 563. Omnibus Computer Graphics, Siggraph Demo '85. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 37)
    [A large montage collection of completely computer-generated visuals including network and cable station ID's; commercial clips; landscapes, etc.]
  - 564. Abel Productions--Computer Graphics. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Aluminum Cans: Aluminum Woman (Box 37)
    - Rockwell International: Entrepreneur (Box 37)
    - Sears Shock Absorber: Steady Rider Gas Shocks (Box 37)
    - Benson & Hedges: Merry Go Round (Box 37)
    - Mercedes Benz: Anti-Locking Brakes (Box 37)
    - STP Oil Treatment: Evolving Images (Box 37)
    - Benson & Hedges: Aquarium (Box 37)
    - Expo '86, Vancouver, B.C.: Flying Tour (Box 37)
    - Amazing Stories: Opening Credits/TV Show (Box 37)
    - Rockwell International: Manage (Box 37)
    - Benson & Hedges: Tiger (Box 37)
    - Sears Tires: Road Handler Construction (Box 37)
    - Rockwell International: Balance (Box 37)
    - Hawaiian Punch: Robot Factory (Box 37)
    - Montage (Box 37)
  - 565. Abel Productions--Computer Graphics. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Aluminum Cans: Aluminum Woman (Box 37)
    - Vodaphone: Car Phone (Box 37)
    - Benson & Hedges: Flute Player (Box 37)
    - Hoover Vacuum: The Cleaning Dimension (Box 37)
    - Benson & Hedges: Aquarium (Box 37)
    - TRW: Max Escher Print (Box 37)
    - Benson & Hedges: Tiger (Box 37)
    - TRW: Computer Ideas (Box 37)
    - Benson & Hedges: Merry Go Round (Box 37)
    - TRW: Historical Drawings (Box 37)
    - Amazing Stories: Opening Credits/TV Show (Box 37)
    - Montage (Box 37)
  - 566. Abel & Associates, Hollywood, California: Atari. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 2:40
    - Atari: Fly/Imagination (black & white) (Box 37)
    - Atari: Fly/Imagination (color) (Box 37)
  - 567. Apple Computers Lemmings. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 38)
    - Apple Computers: Lemmings (Box 38)
  - 568. The Apple Computer (Japan). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Apple Computers: 1984 (Box 38)
    - Apple Computers: Lemmings (Box 38)
  - [569: Missing] (Box 38)
  - 570. Apple (2), Apple II GS (4), Apple Macintosh (5), Campbell Soup. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Apple: Power (Box 38)
    - Apple: Teach (Box 38)
    - Apple II GS: Influences (Box 38)
    - Apple II GS: History Final (Box 38)
    - Apple: Experts (Box 38)
    - Apple: 2-Sided Brain (Box 38)
    - Apple Macintosh: Improvements (Box 38)
    - Apple Macintosh: Going to Work (Box 38)
    - Apple Macintosh: The Red-Eye (Box 38)
    - Apple Macintosh: The Report (Box 38)
    - Apple Macintosh: The Rivalry (Box 38)
    - Campbell's Soup: Space Creature (Box 38)
  - 571. Ad-Video Issue #5: Marketing High-Tech, Looking at Apple & IBM; The Making of 1984. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [A story of the evolution and emergence of Apple into the IBM market. Marketing/advertising strategy in the early '80s for Apple against IBM and IBM's indtroduction of personal computers. The IBM/Charlie Chaplin pairing. The Apple/1984 phenomenon. Problems with the IBM PC Jr. Comany images/targets/attitudes. New competitors and their impact. The making of 1984: explanation of the execution of Apple's 1984 commercial.]
    - Apple Macintosh: 1984 (Box 38)
    - IBM-PC: Rollerskating (Box 38)
  - 572. John Cleese--Compaq Computers (x2). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Compaq Computers: John Cleese/Bruno (Box 38)
    - Compaq Computers: John Cleese/Mr. Prince (Box 38)
  - [573: Missing] (Box 38)
  - 574. IBM: High Performance, Crosswalk (Charlie Chaplin). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - IBM PC AT: Charlie Chaplin/High Performance (Box 38)
    - IBM PC: Charlie Chaplin/Crosswalk (Box 38)
  - 575. Kodak, DiscCamera, Jigsaw. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 00:30
    - Kodak Disc Camera: Jigsaw (Box 38)
  - 576. Kodak, Statue of Liberty. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 00:30
    - Kodak: Statue of Liberty (Box 38)
  - 577. Kodak XOV. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Kodak Video Tape: Floating Video (Box 38)
    - Kodak Video Tape: Floating Video w/SFX (Box 38)
  - 578. Revised Kodak Line Test with Sound. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 38)
  - 579. Kodak 20/20 Segment on MTV. 1983. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 38)
    [Impact of video on pop music adn how MTV is at the center of it.]
  - 580. Creative Review, McCann Madrid (Animatics): Kodak, Paper, The Couple; Kodak, Paper, Backside. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Kodak: The Couple (Box 38)
    - Kodak: Backside (Box 38)
  - 581. Kodak Canada Inc, Christmas. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 00:30
    - Kodak: Christmas (Box 38)
  - 582. Kodak Corporate--Japan. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Kodak: Earth (Box 38)
    - Kodak: Dreams (Box 38)
    - Kodak: Tsutomu (Box 38)
    - Kodak: Dali (Mouth) (Box 38)
    - Kodak: Madonna (Box 38)
    - Kodak: Work (Box 38)
    - Kodak: Drive (Box 38)
    - Kodak: Dali (Eye) (Box 38)
  - 583. Kodak Y&R International: Italy 85, Spain 85. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 5:00
    - VR Film: Alder (Box 38)
    - VR Film: Katze (Box 38)
    - VR Film: Luchs (Box 38)
    - VR Film: Eule (Box 38)
    - VR Film: Luftballon (Box 38)
    - VR Film: Glück (Box 38)
    - Atco Developing: 2 Painters (Box 38)
    - Ektachrome: 3 Swimmers (Box 38)
    - Ektachrome: 3 Swimmers (Box 38)
    - Ektachrome: 3 Swimmers (Box 38)
    - Paper/Film: Album (Box 38)
    - Paper/Film: Album (Box 38)
    - Disc Camera: Dinner (Box 38)
    - Kodacolor VR: Pinball Game (Box 38)
    - Kodacolor VR: Pinball Game (Box 38)
    - Kodacolor Paper: Woman/Spy/Chimp (Box 38)
    - Kodacolor Paper: Scuba/Dance/Chimp (Box 38)
    - Collezione: man's Voice from woman (Box 38)
    - Fotopremio: Helicopter Viewpoint (Box 38)
  - 584. Eastman Kodak Video Cassettes: To the Moon, Memories. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 1:00 (Box 39)
    - Kodak Video Cassettes: To the Moon (Box 39)
    - Kodak Video Cassettes: Memories (not for air) (Box 39)
  - 585. Light Camera Politics, Richard Reives. 1980. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 39)
    [An ABC News closeup on political coverage on television. Heavy use of ABC, NBC, CBS 1980 Presidential election coverage. Richard Reeves reports on his 20 years experience in political coverage, adnhow television has changed the political process, from the beginning of new coverage in the late '50s to the modern coverage of today. National leaders used to control everything, but television took that away. Television changed government during Watergate, but after that, politics changed to suit television.]
  - 586. Digital Productions--Andy Adkin. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [A collection of computer-generated graphics/artwork for various advertisements.]
    - Rockwell International: Entrepreneur (Box 39)
    - Rockwell International: Manage (Box 39)
    - Rockwell International: Balance (Box 39)
    - Montage (Box 39)
    - Rock Video: Mick Jagger/Hard Woman (Box 39)
  - 587. The Electronic Sell, Version 2. 1981. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 39)
    [No narration. A montage collection of examples of the many ways television and modern electronics sells much more than products. It sells lifestyle, images, fashion, music, fantasy, stardom, feelings, etc.]
  - 588. 1 Spot: Nynex. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - NYNEX Yellow Pages: Furniture Stripper (Box 39)
  - 589. Xerox: Father Dominic. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Xerox 9200: Brother Dominic (Box 39)
  - 590. Sony--Handycam. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 00:30
    - Sony Handycam: Moving Snapshots (Box 39)
  - 591. Sony Watchman Big Ape. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 00:55
    - Sony Watchman TV: Big Ape (Box 39)
    - Sony Watchman TV: Big Ape (Box 39)
  - 592. Merrill Lynch AT&T. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 00:30
    - Merrill Lynch: AT&T (Box 39)
  - 593. New Jersey Bell, AT&T, Southern Bell, Bell. 1983. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 2:00
    - New Jersey Bell: Changes (Box 39)
    - AT&T Phone Center: New Name (Box 39)
    - AT&T: New Technology (Box 39)
    - Southwestern Bell: Map/Regional (Box 39)
    - Wisconsin Telephone: Company Change (Box 39)
  - 594. Keep Britain Tidy. 1983. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 39)
  - 595. National Urban Coalition: Give A Damn. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - National Urban Coalition: Send Your Kid to a Ghetto (Box 39)
    - National Urban Coalition: Lloyd Bridges/Give a Damn (Box 39)
    - National Urban Coalition: What Do You Want to Be When You Grow Up? (Box 39)
    - National Urban Coalition: Landlord (Box 39)
  - 596. AIDS TV Commercials. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 9:47 (Box 39)
  - 597. Belgium Condom Commercial. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Durex Condoms: Parked Roadside (Belgium) (Box 39)
  - 598. AIDS Prevention: The Grim Reaper. 1987. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 39)
  - 599. AIDS Commercila Europa (Norwegen). 1987. Umatic. TRT: 1:13 (Box 40)
  - 600. American Cancer Socity; Sanka (3). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - American Cancer Society: Yul Brenner (Box 40)
    - Sanka Decaf: Lena Horne (Box 40)
    - Sanka Decaf: Dorothy Hamill (Box 40)
    - Sanka Decaf: John Newcombe (Box 40)
  - 601. BVU Cassette of Drugs Commercials 1985 -1986. 1985-1986. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - Drugs Misuse: Control (Box 40)
    - Drugs Misuse: Dummy (Box 40)
    - Try It (Box 40)
    - Invitation (Box 40)
  - 602. Scottish Health Education--Anti-Drugs: Be All You Can Be. 1985. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 40)
  - 603. Agence McCann Erickson: Anti-Drogue. 1986. Umatic. PAL. TRT: 1:00 (Box 40)
  - 604. Anti-Drug Abuse Advertising (Spain). Undated. Umatic. TRT: 17:00
    - Cruz Roja: Become a Member of the Red Cross (Box 40)
  - 605. 4 Drug Offensive TVC--Australia. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 3:00
    - Australian Federal Government: Drug Offensive (Box 40)
  - 606. Drugs. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Nancy Reagan Address to Ad Council (Box 40)
    - Anti-Drugs: Kids/Just Say No (Box 40)
    - Anti-Drugs: Try It/Just Say No (Box 40)
    - Anti-Drugs: 12 Year Old/Just Say No (Box 40)
    - Anti-Drugs: Spanish Child/Just Say No (Box 40)
    - Anti-Drugs: Bridge Walk/Heroin Screws You Up (Box 40)
    - Anti-Drugs: Lockers/Just Say No (Box 40)
    - Cocaine. The Big Lie: Howard (Box 40)
    - Cocaine. The Big Lie: Rose C. (Box 40)
    - Cocaine. The Big Lie: William O'Donnell, Jr. (Box 40)
    - Cocaine. The Big Lie: Lydia R. (Box 40)
    - Cocaine. The Big Lie: Reggie Jackson (Box 40)
  - 607. Yellowhammer Anti-Heroin Campaign. Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 40)
  - 608. Muscles: Marcy Exerciser, Pabst Light Beer, RC 100 Cola, D.P. Gympac. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Marcy Exerciser: Every Morning (Box 40)
    - Pabst Light Beer: Beer Bellies (Box 40)
    - RC 100 Cola: Body Talk (Box 40)
    - D.P. Gympac: Heartbeat (Box 40)
  - 609. Robert Abel: Miniature and Model Demo Reel. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Levi's: Devil Engine (Box 40)
    - Sprint: High Tech (Box 40)
    - TransAmerica: King Kong (Box 40)
    - Braun: Model 2000 (Box 40)
    - Rubbermaid: Ultimate Microwave Cookware (Box 40)
    - Excedrin: Floating Capsule (Box 40)
    - Levi's: One Way Cords (Box 40)
    - Montage (Box 40)
    - ITT: Growing Cities (Box 40)
  - 610. Robert Abel: Computer Graphics Demo Reel. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - TRW: Exchanging Ideas (Box 40)
    - MaxFli: Energy (Box 40)
    - TRW: Changing Pictures (Box 40)
    - CBS: Election '84 (Box 40)
    - NE Telephone: Network (Box 40)
    - TRW: Line (Box 40)
    - Montage (Box 40)
    - TRW: Ripple (Box 40)
    - High Fidelity: Credits/Dancers (Box 40)
  - 611. Robert Abel: General Reel. 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Data General (Box 40)
    - Pepsi: Whisper (Box 40)
    - Adidas (Box 40)
    - NFPA: Brilliance (Box 40)
    - Jovan: Good Girl/Bad Girl (Box 40)
    - Ford: Ride and Handling (Box 40)
    - Okidata: Decisions (Box 40)
    - Lucky Strike: Diner (Box 40)
    - Memorex: Slight Exaggeration (Box 40)
    - Panasonic: Sounds (Box 40)
    - Volkswagen: GTI (Box 40)
    - TRW: Ripple (Box 40)
    - Apple: Factory (Box 40)
    - Hoover: Dimension (Box 40)
    - ITT: Growing Cities (Box 40)
    - Pepsi: Nuns (Box 40)
    - NYNEX: Traffic Jam (Box 40)
    - Levi's: Be There Pig (Box 40)
  - 612. 3 Spots: Calvin Klein Obsession, Memorex, Continental. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Calvin Klein Obsession for Men: On Trial (Box 40)
    - Memorex: Desert/Movie (Box 40)